{
    "subject": "resource/WLW",
    "predicate": "ontology/broadcastNetwork",
    "object": "resource/Cincinnati_Reds_Radio_Network",
    "human_readable": "WLW broadcasts on Cincinnati Reds Radio Network.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9530714750289917,
            "question": "Name a radio station that broadcasts on the Cincinnati Reds Radio Network."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9026768803596497,
            "question": "What team's games are broadcast on the Cincinnati Reds Radio Network?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9003979563713074,
            "question": "On which radio network does WLW broadcast?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8813463449478149,
            "question": "Which sport does the Cincinnati Reds Radio Network primarily broadcast?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8134205937385559,
            "question": "Where is the Cincinnati Reds Radio Network based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7967868447303772,
            "question": "What station broadcasts Cincinnati Reds games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5811028480529785,
            "question": "What is the primary focus of the Cincinnati Reds Radio Network?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5434044003486633,
            "question": "What type of programming does the Cincinnati Reds Radio Network primarily feature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38054943084716797,
            "question": "Is WLW affiliated with a sports team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3267483115196228,
            "question": "Does WLW cover local sporting events?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WLW broadcasts on Cincinnati Reds Radio Network.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5302_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is WLW affiliated with a sports team?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5302_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of programming does the Cincinnati Reds Radio Network primarily feature?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5302_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary focus of the Cincinnati Reds Radio Network?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5302_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5302_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5302_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5302_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5302_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5302_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5302_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5302_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5302_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5302_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5302_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the required format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that multiple documents mention that WLW (700 AM) is the flagship station for the Cincinnati Reds Radio Network, and that all Reds games will continue to be broadcast live on WLW."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that WLW (700 AM) is the flagship station for the Cincinnati Reds and a part of their radio network, providing regular broadcasts of Reds games. Therefore, the statement \"WLW broadcasts on Cincinnati Reds Radio Network\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}